Kanyon Wyman

3037 Cascades Trail SE Rio Rancho, NM 87124 (828) 280-3295 kanyonwyman@gmail.com

Objective

To apply my natural talent and passion for working with computers to helping people resolve their challenges in an efficient and professional way, and to continually expand my knowledge and experience with computers and software solutions.

Experience & Skills

A+ Certification, TC Roberson High School

Experience in cyber security, hardware and software troubleshooting, computer building, some experience in video and picture editing and web design

Problem solving, devising solutions and assisting with implementation

Work Experience

Rush Tech Support, Hypoluxo, Florida

Escalated Technician — DECEMBER 2016 - AUGUST 2017

- Worked on escalated fixes that other technicians couldn't solve, utilizing Powershell, Tweaking and OS Installations
- Connected clients remotely via TeamViewer or LogMeIn
- Found reasoning for client problems and devised the most efficient solutions
- Sold computer software and subscriptions
- Fixed networking bugs and set up networks for clients

Sales — JULY 2016 - DECEMBER 2016

- Telephone sales of computer software and tech support warranties
- One of top salespersons

Additional Work History

MAY 2018 - SEPT 2018	Line Cook, Mayfel's, Asheville, NC
FEB 2018 - MAY 2018	Line Cook, Hickory Tavern, Asheville, NC
DEC 2017 - FEB 2018	Line Cook, Bier Garden, Asheville, NC
SEPT 2017 - DEC 2017	Delivery Driver, Jimmy Johns, Asheville, NC

Education

2015 - AB Tech Community College, Asheville, NC - GED